question_data =[
    {"category": "Entertainment: Cartoon & Animations", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In the &quot;Shrek&quot; film franchise, Donkey is played by Eddie Murphy.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                       "question": "The music group Daft Punk got their name from a negative review they recieved.",
                                       "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The main character in the &quot;Half-Life&quot; franchise is named Morgan Freeman.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Han Solo&#039;s co-pilot and best friend, &quot;Chewbacca&quot;, is an Ewok.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Greenland is almost as big as Africa.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The music video to The Buggle&#039;s &quot;Video Killed the Radio Star&quot; was the first music video to broadcast on MTV.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "San Marino is the only country completely surrounded by another country.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                      "question": "The Spitfire originated from a racing plane.",
                                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "&quot;Undertale&quot; is an RPG created by Toby Fox and released in 2015.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Animals", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                       "question": "Kangaroos keep food in their pouches next to their children.",
                                       "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science: Computers", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The logo for Snapchat is a Bell.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Nutella is produced by the German company Ferrero.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                      "question": "There are 6 legendary cards in &quot;Clash Royale&quot;.",
                                      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Sports", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Peyton Manning retired after winning Super Bowl XLIX.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                      "question": "Niko Bellic is the protagonist of Grand Theft Auto IV.",
                                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In Kingdom Hearts the Paopu fruit is said to intertwine the destinies for two people forever.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Comics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Deadpool&#039;s identity is Slade Wilson.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "No Game No Life first aired in 2014.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The 2005 video game &quot;Call of Duty 2: Big Red One&quot; is not available on PC.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In the &quot;Half-Life&quot; series, &quot;H.E.V&quot; stands for &quot;Hazardous Evasiveness Vest&quot;",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "St. Louis is the capital of the US State Missouri.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                      "question": "Adolf Hitler was born in Australia. ", "correct_answer": "False",
                                      "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science: Computers", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In most programming languages, the operator ++ is equivalent to the statement &quot;+= 1&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "When you cry in space, your tears stick to your face.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In the &quot;Toaru Kagaku no Railgun&quot; anime,  espers can only reach a maximum of level 6 in their abilities.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Sports", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Roger Federer is a famous soccer player.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Romanian belongs to the Romance language family, shared with French, Spanish, Portuguese and Italian. ",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "An exothermic reaction is a chemical reaction that releases energy by radiating electricity.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "An Astronomical Unit is the distance between Earth and the Moon.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                      "question": "In Pok&eacute;mon, Bulbasaur is the only starter pokemon that is a Grass\/Poison type.",
                                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Animals", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "A caterpillar has more muscles than humans do.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                       "question": "Brandon Routh plays the titular character in the movie &quot;John Wick&quot;.",
                                       "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The Konami Code is known as Up, Up, Down, Down, Left, Right, Right, Left, B, A, Start.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Politics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "One of Barack Obama&#039;s United States presidential campaign slogan&#039;s was &quot;Yes We Can&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Daft Punk originated in France.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Stevie Wonder&#039;s real name is Stevland Hardaway Morris.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In RuneScape, one must complete the &quot;Dragon Slayer&quot; quest before equipping Rune Platelegs.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In &quot;Star Trek&quot;, Klingons are aliens.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                       "question": "Actor Tommy Chong served prison time.", "correct_answer": "True",
                                       "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The sum of any two odd integers is odd.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The National Animal of Scotland is the Unicorn.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                       "question": "Thomas Crapper was a plumber who invented the flushing toilet.",
                                       "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Vehicles", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "BMW M GmbH is a subsidiary of BMW AG that focuses on car performance.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                       "question": "In 1993, Prince changed his name to an unpronounceable symbol because he was unhappy with his contract with Warner Bros.",
                                       "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Codemasters is the developer of the Gran Turismo series.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                      "question": "In the video game &quot;Splatoon&quot;, the playable characters were originally going to be rabbits instead of squids.",
                                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The game &quot;Jetpack Joyride&quot; was created by &quot;Redbrick Studios&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Lead Singer Rivers Cuomo of American rock band Weezer attended Harvard.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In Resident Evil 4, the Chicago Typewriter has infinite ammo.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
